Robin Gupta

Asstt. Manager - Enterprise Sales

Summary

An energetic, ambitious and enthusiastic professional who has prior experience of maintaining existing client relationships and generating new ones. Possesses exquisite verbal communication and organizational skills. Skills Set- Business development, Telecom sales, corporate sales, team handling, nd campaign managment, digital media solutions

Experience

Asstt. Mgr - Sales at mGage LLC March 2013 - Present (2 years 4 months)

We bring 15+ years of global mobile marketing and mCRM experience to the industry from our teams across the U.S., U.K. and India. We empower customer interactions at all stages of the lifecycle, from acquisition through retention. Our unique data analytics platform provides insight that no other mobile marketing company can offer, measuring the full effectiveness of your campaign from pre to post click interactions. Fortune 1000 companies use our products and solutions across the globe and we have global Omni channel connectivity. mGage was purchased by GSO Capital Partners LP, a division of Blackstone Group LP, in January 2014.

Area sales manager - North at Value First Digital Media Pvt Ltd January 2012 - March 2013 (1 year 3 months)

Was responsible for sales in Delhi/NCR - specifically Gurgaon. Enabling Enterprise Mobility (Two way communication via SMS, Voice, WAP, Long code, Short code. Specialist in turning lost business into revenue giving client for company, specially working on acquiring key accounts for clients.

2 recommendations available upon request

Sr .Associate Enterprise Sale-north at Value First messaging Pvt Ltd 2012 - 2012 (less than a year)

1) corporate sales To identify or pitch corporate in the defined territory of operation To pitch ValueFirst products and services to the corporate and convert them into clients and generate revenue To achieve, monthly, quarterly and revenue targets on revenue and client acquisition To build relationships with multiple departments of clients and increase their transactions

Manager-Campus Relations at Aspiring Minds Assessment Pvt Ltd February 2010 - June 2011 (1 year 5 months)

Handled the Campus & Institutional sales to B.Tech, MBA, MCA campuses across whole of Rajasthan+Mumbai,earlier South india with a view to provide equal opportunities to the freshers in the campus with top corporates. Organising the talent acquisition event for the corporates Responsibilities & Duties Get Business from all Clients in Rajasthan as Territory Providing Operation and Marketing efficiencies Main Retention of Old Clients and make them in profitable Assest for Company Strategy For sales

1 recommendation available upon request

Certifications

AMCAT Certified Business Analyst

Aspiring Minds License 42636-94 September 2014

AMCAT Certified in English Comprehension

Aspiring Minds License 42636-283 November 2014

Courses

Master of Business Administration (MBA),

Marketing

EMPI business school

NIIT Advance Excel course for indepth analysis

Languages

Sanskrit

Punjabi

Skills & Expertise

VAS

Mobile Devices

SMS

Integration

Key Account Management

Team Management

Negotiation

Closing Deals

Deal Closure

Sales

Marketing

Sales Operations

Strategy

Management

Marketing Strategy

Leadership

Enterprise Software

Education

EMPI business school

Master of Business Administration (MBA), Marketing, 2008 - 2010

Activities and Societies: Inter school quiz organized by NEN

Panjab University

Bachelor of Commerce (BCom), Econom, 2004 - 2007

Honors and Awards

National level Boxing silver medalist, represented Chandigarh cricket team at national level. winner in SKIT at college. Been part of group leads to expedition - Leh ladkakh and Goa from Chandigarh Interests

cricket, soccer, incubation of new ideas

Robin Gupta

Asstt. Manager - Enterprise Sales



3 people have recommended Robin

"Tank of positive energy! Hard core sales person, specialist in strategy planning. Has complete thorough knowledge about his work. Always coming up with new wonderful ideas for creating new revenue streams. Master in building business relationships with customer. Keeps an eye on every aspect of the sales. On personal front, Robin is a nice gentleman and I am happy to say he is a very good friend of mine. I wish him very best for his future:)"

- Tarun Gupta, Enterprise Sales, Value First Digital Media Pvt. Ltd., worked directly with Robin at Value First Digital Media Pvt Ltd
- "1. Robin is a very motivational and inspirational leader. . He has a very organized and structured thought process, where he will always have the facts and figures handy to backup his view points. His exposure to the industry is enormous and Complete package of "Know How" and Execution of the job at hand is what defines him best! A full knowledge repository with an eye to monetize the ideas into reality!!. He is very creative in his problem solving abilities and the solutions he prescribes are always relevant to the current market trends and the best practices across the industry. He's sure to be an asset to any organization he associates with. Its indeed a pleasure know him personally and work professionally with him!! All the best!! :)"
- Raghu Marwaha, Account management, One97 Communications Limited, was with another company when working with Robin at Value First Digital Media Pvt Ltd
- "I had the privilege of working in a team with Robin. I remember we used to have daily team meetings in Zonal manager's cabin. We used to come out of the meeting with positive thoughts, ready to face the challenges. Robin is a leader/ manager who works with the team and brings out the best in every member of the team."
- Apoorv Saxena, PMP, Campus Relation Manager, Aspiring Minds Pvt Ltd, worked directly with Robin at Aspiring Minds Assessment Pvt Ltd

Contact Robin on LinkedIn